<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on ATG e-Power -  Smart charging solution, Charging For Your life</title>
    <link>https://atg-epower.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on ATG e-Power -  Smart charging solution, Charging For Your life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 18:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://atg-epower.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://atg-epower.github.io/post/2023-01-03-privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atg-epower.github.io/post/2023-01-03-privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>In this Privacy Policy we inform you about how we process your personal information, whether you are a visitor to our website, a purchaser of our electric vehicle charging stations, or a user of electric vehicle charging stations on ATG e-Power Network.
Except as explicitly provided herein, this Policy applies to your use of the ATG e-Power website (the “Website”), the ATG e-Power mobile application (the “App”), and to any service offered by ATG e-Power that includes a link to this Policy, including your ATG e-Power account (if you have registered or are registering your account) and the ATG e-Power radio-frequency identification cards (the “RFID cards”) (each of these services and applications are collectively defined as the “Service”).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service</title>
      <link>https://atg-epower.github.io/post/2023-01-03-terms-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atg-epower.github.io/post/2023-01-03-terms-service/</guid>
      <description>THESE TERMS OF USE APPLY TO YOUR USE OF THE ATG e-Power WEBSITE, MOBILE APPLICATION, PLATFORM AND/OR CHARGING SERVICE. By using any of these Services, you confirm that you accept and comply with these terms of use (“Terms”). If you do not agree to these Terms, you should not use these Services.
1. Who we are and how to contact us The Services are offered to you by ATG Electronics Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
